

## CONTACT



+57 319 576 97 90



duvano30496@hotmail.com



Bogotá, Colombia



Portfolio www.addevsoft.netlify.app



www.github.com/DuvanHB



LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/duvanhernandez

## SKILLS

HTML & CSS

TypeScript - JavaScript

Angular



C#.Net Core



SQL Server 

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

SPANISH

# Duván Hernández Barrios Software Engineer

Electronic engineer from the Francisco José de Caldas District University, experienced in web and mobile application development. Good knowledge in HTML, CSS and TypeScript, experience in Angular and Ionic frameworks for the frontend, knowledge of the Redux data handling pattern. Knowledge of C# with the .NET Core framework for the backend.

Management of relational databases with SQL server.

Solid knowledge in the JavaScript language. With innovation, conceptual thinking, initiative and results orientation.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Senior Software Engineer**

October 2021- present

Creation of web and mobile applications for the frontend with Angular Creation of services or business logic in the backend with .Net core Database management with Sql Server Technologies used: TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Angular, .Net Core, Sql Server.

## Angular development engineer

March 2021- October 2021

Global Hitss

Creation of web and mobile applications for the frontend with Angular Technologies used: TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Angular.

#### Junior development engineer

February 2020- March 2021

Intergrupo

Development of applications with Angular for the frontend.

Business logic for the backend with .Net Core.

Database with Sql server.

Technologies used: TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Angular, .Net Core, Sql Server.

#### Internship

August 2019- February 2020

Intergrupo

Creation of web and mobile applications for the frontend with Angular.

Technologies used: TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Angular.

### **EDUCATION**

#### **Electronic Engineer**

January 2014- August 2020

Francisco José de Caldas District University

Bachelor

February 2002- December 2013

Alejandro Obregón High School

# **OTHER STUDIES**

Course: Modern JavaScript 20 hours Course: HTML & CSS 40 hours Course: Angular from zero to expert 50 hours

**Course: Git version control** 15 hours Course: C#, .Net core 20 hours

Certification: Azure fundamental Microsoft AZ-900 Certification: Programming in C# Microsoft 20-483